1st-movers.com 2016-04-21

# Privacy Policy - Extly Extensions

Extly Extensions is committed to protecting you and your personal information when you are using our services. We want our services to safe and enjoyable environments for our users. This Privacy Policy is relevant to our use of any personal information you provide to us during your visit to our site.

Extly Extensions seeks to follow the industry's best practices concerning personal information handling.

#### Personal information collected

We may collect the following information:

  * Name and contact information including email address.
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers. 
  * Website URL where our component installed.

#### Use of collected information

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * Improving our products and services.
  * Sending promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information.

#### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### Use of cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

  * Google Analytics: This cookie allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. Using Google Analytics we can see what content is popular on our website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching. 
  * Google Adwords: Using Google Adwords code we are able to see which pages helped lead to an action taken by a visitor (conversion). This allows us to make better use of our paid search budget.
  * DoubleClick: We use remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages, allowing us to provide targeted advertising in the future.

#### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following way: If you don't agree to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [team@extly.com](mailto:team@extly.com)

**We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.**

We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

Join the Club!

Access and support services to all Extly's extensions for 1-Year. The Extly Club is your source for all of our extensions.

Copyright © 2007-2016 Extly.com - Joomla! Extensions. All Rights Reserved.

Joomla! name is used under a limited license from Open Source Matters in the United States and other countries. Extly.com is not affiliated with or endorsed by Open Source Matters or the Joomla! project.
